(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-02T01:17:46.683280",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
私醜いから恋をしている 鮮やかなる花に見惚れている
I'm in love despite being ugly, gazing at vivid flowers in awe.
まるで嵐の通った後みたいな顔で
With a face like the aftermath of a storm,
アナタは目見麗しい人だから醜い私には恋をしない
You're so breathtakingly fair, you'd never love someone as unsightly as me.
化粧じゃ隠せないの
Makeup can't hide it,
生来の不出来さ
This innate flaw of mine.
Remember the names of this episode, rises on a moonlit stage
Ignore your cause away, no prayers begin those days
Looking for apples placed, not what's more than just a pretty face
Poison grace, poison snakes, cut the rates, cut the brakes
It's gotta be the way you carry yourself, so disown all of the royalties and allies as well
If riches spoil me and you, we should bury ourselves
So you can sneak on top of a throne by honeys, style and stealth
So Empress 心におわす Empress
So Empress, reigning within my heart, Empress,
どうかお与えください
Please bestow it upon me.
Empress Empress Empress Empress
Wake up, Empress in me!
さあ玉座を空けなさい
Now clear the throne!
誰だって老いていく朝な夕な
Everyone grows older, morning and night.
どんなに頑丈でも ほら
No matter how sturdy, look,
背筋が伸びてきたでしょ
your posture has straightened up, right?
肺から作った
Made from the lungs,
このティアラ そろそろ誰が
this tiara—soon, who
本物なのか 教えてあげなくちゃ
is the real deal? You've got to tell me.
邪魔な髪は切った ちょっと無敵だった
I cut my bothersome hair, I was a bit invincible.
Now Marine's on a high-speed chase, faces real for rent,
慈悲深い目で上書き
Overwriting with merciful eyes,
How can I make you interested in me?
Can’t you do me a favor for once?
Can't you do me a favor for once?
僕のため歌って
Sing for my sake.
例えるなら ひかり色 形の変わらないしあわせ
Like a beacon of light, happiness that never changes shape.
愛は無限大 壊れても大丈夫 僕しかいない君になってよ
Love is infinite, it's okay if it breaks. Be mine and mine alone!
僕ナシじゃ生きていけないほど
To the point where you can't live without me,
壊れてもなおせばいい
if it breaks, you can just fix it.
君が好きな僕が欲しいでしょ
You want the me that you love, right?
Give me your love あいしてる
Give me your love, I love you.
胎児のときから 決まってたのプリンセス
Decided since we were fetuses, a princess.
それはいつか スピンオフ
That's someday a spin-off.
僕の願いなんて 聞く気もないようなの
It seems you have no intention of hearing my wish.
仕方ないね Witch Hunt
It can't be helped, a Witch Hunt.
たった一つの存在理由を
Give me the one and only reason for existence
僕へとください君から
from you to me.
時にすれ違い 育んだ愛が欲しい
I want the love nurtured through our moments apart.
健やかに眠る愛しその腕に抱く君が見たい
I want to see you held in those arms, sleeping soundly.
口は僕 鼻は君 そんな未来がもう見えるよ
Mouth is me, nose is you, I can already see such a future.
Give me your love あいしてる
Give me your love, I love you.
しあわせになりましょう 誰のものにもならないで
Let's be happy, don't belong to anyone else.
Give me your love 僕のもとへおいて
Give me your love, keep me by your side.
愛は無限大 壊れても大丈夫
Love is infinite, it's okay if it breaks.
僕しかいない君になってよ
Be the you who has only me.
僕ナシじゃ生きていけないほど
To the point where you can't live without me,
初めてのキスをしよう 真実の愛が欲しいでしょ
let's have our first kiss. You want true love, right?
Give me your love あいしてる
Give me your love, I love you.
どんなに頑丈でも ほら 背筋が伸びてきたでしょ
No matter how sturdy, look, your posture has straightened up, right?
肺から作った このティアラ
Made from the lungs, this tiara—
そろそろ誰が 本物なのか 教えてあげなくちゃ
soon, who is the real deal? You've got to tell me.
分からせてあげましょう 優しく
Let's make you understand, gently.
It's the truth that I knew was real all along
something's wrong, guess I gotta show you my appeal!
Wake me up, make me up
wake me up, make me up
Wake me up
皆さん、ようこそCalliope誕生日ライブへ！
Welcome everybody, to this year's live show!
ARCANA
The ARCANA is the means by which all is revealed...
Is it not, Persona?
I know you guys know what I'm talking about, right?
Check it out, first of all, this stage.
Stage, yeah, staginess, huh?
Look, we're in a crystal ball!
Can you believe it? This was all Mori's idea...
Well, we'll figure it out. But in the meantime...
I have assembled all of these tarot cards here.
Tarot cards featuring my friends!
For example, we have Marine Senchou...
Thank you so much to Gumshrew for drawing these...
I decided to pick Arcana that fit my friends...
そうですね、今日は Mori Calliope だけの曲歌います。
That's right, today I'm singing Mori Calliope songs only.
And I tried to pick songs that fit the Arcana...
So we have some amazing guests lined up today...
Thank you so much, everybody, for dropping by...
And you know what? You can continue to be a part of it.
How can you do that? By using the hashtag!
Use the hashtag, okay?
The hashtag that we have decided upon for this show, okay?
So make sure that you use that and then type your impressions, right?
You guys love the internet, you're always doing stuff on it and saying silly stuff here and there and everywhere.
You guys love the internet, always doing stuff on it and saying silly stuff.
Go ahead and, you know, upload screenshots and your thoughts and impressions and I'll read them.
Go ahead and upload screenshots and your thoughts and impressions, and I'll read them.
I'll read them later once I've, you know, calmed down and stuff like that, you know, because we got a show to do, right?
I'll read them later once I've calmed down, because we got a show to do, right?
We got a show to do!
Let's try and have as much fun as we can while we are stuck here in this crystal ball together for Mori's birthday, yes!
Let's have as much fun as we can while stuck here together for Mori's birthday!
And it's Mori's birthday, so you know that we've got announcements, right? Stick till the end
And since it's her birthday, we've got announcements, right? Stick till the end
because we got a couple really big ones coming up and you don't want to miss them. If you want, you don't have to, but, but if you want to,
because we got a couple really big ones coming up and you don't want to miss them.
You should. You should stay, stick around, hang out with us. It's gonna be fun!
you should. Stay, stick around, hang out with us. It's gonna be fun!
Ah, what kind of songs can you expect to hear, I wonder? Only some of Mori's favorites.
What kind of songs can you expect to hear? Only some of Mori's favorites.
Yes, there are actually mostly guests. I think there's maybe one solo song, but, but almost every single song has a guest.
Yes, there are mostly guests. I think there's maybe one solo song, but almost every single song has a guest.
Wow, probably the most guests that I've ever had in in any live that I've ever done. All guests and also very few MCs.
Wow, probably the most guests I've ever had in any live I've ever done. All guests and also very few MCs.
That's right, we're going to be too focused on performing, so get ready to not hear a lot of talking.
That's right, we'll be too focused on performing, so get ready to not hear a lot of talking.
But there's going to be lots of singing and dancing.
Why am I being goofy? This isn't how I'm supposed to be on stage. It's supposed to be goofy during streams and then goofy on stage.
Why am I being goofy? This isn't how I'm supposed to be on stage. Supposed to be goofy during streams, but serious on stage.
I can't help myself. I can't help myself. I'm a dummy. What can I say?
But I can't help myself. I'm a dummy. What can I say?
Don't say that. Don't put yourself down, Mori. The MC is going off the rails, so we better just continue singing at this point.
Don't put yourself down, Mori. The MC is going off the rails, so we better just continue singing.
Or else I'm going to say something even more stupid. Yes, I love MCs, deadvibe, you guys know this. I really don't love MCs.
Or else I'll say something even more stupid. Yes, I love MCs, deadbeats, you know this. I really don't love MCs.
Let the show go on, yeah?
Oh, but first I have to summon the next guest.
That's right. The next guest I will be bringing forward with this tarot card. As you can see, these are very powerful. So, let's go ahead and call the next person and get this show rolling.
That's right. The next guest I will bring forward with this tarot card. As you can see, these are very powerful. Let's call the next person and get this show rolling!
Tada!
興味 ない もって ない やって ない し 感じ ない 勘違い
Uninterested, holding nothing, doing nothing, not even feeling it
how did it get to this ? no regrets , we 'll just run into the night
How did it get to this? No regrets, we'll just run into the night
boxed in , the walls cracking , lemme out
Boxed in, the walls cracking, lemme out
i 'm losing grip , i fall back and take a bow
I'm losing grip, I fall back and take a bow
missed hits and pitfalls of living loud
prefaced it with " time is limited so do it now "
Prefaced it with "time is limited so do it now"
出口 ない まま 置い て 行 かれ た 紙 と 声 叫び つづける
Left behind with no exit, paper and voice keep screaming
誰 か が 気づい て くれる まで
Until someone notices
days i can 't get up , my soul moves just a little , a little
Days I can't get up, my soul moves just a little, a little
an isolated voice reminds “ i can turn the tide ”
An isolated voice reminds "I can turn the tide"
let sunlight leak inside the room just a little , a little
Let sunlight leak inside the room just a little, a little
i find it harder to be strong , and as i go along
I find it harder to be strong, and as I go along
i 'm falling out of touch
I'm falling out of touch
seek out your fire , re - ignite your flame
Seek out your fire, re-ignite your flame
no more living sick and tired , no apologies required , and i know
No more living sick and tired, no apologies required, and I know
maybe thеre ’ s no one els е who feels the same
Maybe there's no one else who feels the same
passion fades but so do scars , we ’ ll paint the future , make it ours
Passion fades, but so do scars, we'll paint the future, make it ours
yeah , yeah , yeah , yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
曖昧 な 日々 でも 意味 ある いける とこ まで いっ て みる だけ
Even ambiguous days have meaning, just trying to go as far as I can
oh , oh , oh , oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh
まだまだ 届い て も ない よ 目 の 前 の その 壁 を 壊せ
Still not reaching it, smash the wall right before my eyes
Passion fades, but so do scars
We'll paint the future, make it ours
品位 欠けた スピーカー 聞く 耳 なんて ない あしかから ず
Speakers lacking class, I've got no ears for you, excuse me.
似て非なる 自信家・自惚れ
Self-proclaimed confident folks who are full of themselves,
紙一重 恐れ慄け
a paper-thin margin, tremble in fear!
Passion fades, but so do scars
We'll paint the future, make it ours
SEEK OUT YOUR FIRE,
RE-IGNITE YOUR FLAME
No more living sick and tired
No apologies required
And I know, yeah, I know
Maybe there's no one else who feels the same
Passion fades, but so do scars
We'll paint the future, make it ours
曖昧な 日々 でも 意味 ある
Even in ambiguous days, there's meaning.
行けるところまでいってみるだけ
I'll just go as far as I can go.
まだまだ届いでもないよ
It's still not reaching you yet,
目の前のその壁を壊せ
smash right through that wall before your eyes!
興味ない 持ってない
No interest, don't care,
やってないし
haven't done it,
感じない感じがはあ
and don't feel a thing, huh.
Look boys and ladies, cat chase, dog chase
Don't evolve, but the kingdom of swingdom is open to all
Until the game ends, a place to make a profit, rap and swing is a thing now, more for you to scoff at
Look boys and ladies, look boys and ladies
Shout out to any crazy people still in the empire, I just want set fire, I'm wishing I went higher
品位 欠けた スピーカー
Speakers lacking class,
聞く耳なんてない あしかからず
I've got no ears for you, excuse me.
似て非なる自信家・自惚れ
Self-proclaimed confident folks who are full of themselves,
紙一重 恐れ慄け
a paper-thin margin, tremble in fear!
誇って縮んじゃ縮んじゃどけ
Flaunt it, shrink back, get out of the way!
権威ぶったハリボテ
A paper-mache facade pretending to be authority,
stupid 道化
stupid jester,
そこ のけ そこ のけ
get out of the way, get out of the way,
shut up 妄言
shut up delusions,
猪口才 な 嘘 の 音
impudent lies sounding off.
ボロ儲けしてるふりが得意なネズミ
A rat whose specialty is pretending to rake in the cash.
香水を振り撒いても消えやしないその汚臭
Even if you spray perfume, that foul stench won't go away.
What's the look for? You a skeptic? Those opinions? Kinda septic!
You're my minions, no, wait, my biggest fans! Internet business women drawing up plans!
Why ya tryin' to pin me for a pyramid scheme? I refuse to be a part of any derelict dreams!
Slide over and hear the screams of naysayers, I'm basically god so get to saying those prayers!
拘りに美学 持ち合わせちゃいけない 無個性の徒
A mob of the individuality-less who can't even pair obsession with aesthetics.
似て非なる自信家・自惚れ
Self-proclaimed confident folks who are full of themselves,
紙一重 恐れ慄け
a paper-thin margin, tremble in fear!
誇って縮んじゃ縮んじゃどけ
Flaunt it, shrink back, get out of the way!
権威ぶったハリボテ
A paper-mache facade pretending to be authority,
勘違いしてる奴らばかりうんざり
Sick and tired of all these folks who misunderstand everything,
だけどあんたの方には傾かない秤
but the scales won't tilt in your favor.
あんたの芝生はまだまだ青臭い
Your lawn is still too green,
刈り取るまでもねえ 助走なし ワンパン
no need to mow it down, a zero-run-up one-punch!
お山の天狗を並べて鼻で笑う
Lining up the mountain tengu and scoffing at them.
虎の威借りパク出来るんならやってごらん
If you can ride on someone else's coattails, let's see you try!
全然物足りない なら掃除も白くはならない
Still completely unsatisfied, so the cleanup won't be clean either.
誇る者久からず
The proud do not last long.
似て非なる自信家・自惚れ
Self-proclaimed confident folks who are full of themselves,
紙一重 恐れ慄け
a paper-thin margin, tremble in fear!
最終警告のすん止め
Stopping right before the final warning,
すらあんたにとっては致死
for you, that alone is fatal.
stupid 道化
stupid jester,
そこ のけ そこ のけ
get out of the way, get out of the way,
shut up 妄言
shut up delusions,
猪口才 な 嘘 の 音
impudent lies sounding off.
ボロ儲けしてるふりが得意なネズミ
A rat whose specialty is pretending to rake in the cash.
香水を振り撒いても消えやしないその汚臭
Even if you spray perfume, that foul stench won't go away.
It starts with just a thought within
A wish that rode on mellow wind
Begins and ends with "hello" and "goodbye"
始まりはそうね 願い乗せるそよ風
It starts, right? A breeze carrying a wish,
"hello"から向かうのは"goodbye"
moving from "hello" to "goodbye".
今何ができるだろう 何になれるだろう
What can I do now? What can I become?
But the high is over sooner than it began
Stay alive and sober, all a part of the plan
I arrived a soldier in a far-off land
With a four-leaf clover in this scarred right hand
You can
Over and over, rewrite
On the winds of desperation
Flying for all this world to see
何を求めるの 運命はもう決められてるのに
What are you searching for, even though fate is already decided?
Numbing pain is numbing happiness
Something anyone can find
Pushing on
For resolve that's truly mine
Alone, it's hopeless, though the soul can say I tried
立ち向かう時には be void inside
when confronting it, be void inside.
Recalling all the days we met
A place that I belonged, and yet
My world was filled with walls of endless height
時を越えていこう いつ日づけ
Crossing through time...
The soul is divided
Colder inside, the dice
Roll is decisive
Must have it nice, a gorgeous device
運命を燃やし尽くして永遠に ここから出て行くために 檻を壊すだけ
Burning up fate for eternity, just to break out of this cage.
On winds of desperation
Flying for all this world to see
Though I make do all despite it
Fate is hard to hide, it's always been decided for me
涙と血の哀悼を 永遠に流れでもまだ足りない
Tears and bloody mourning flowing endlessly, still not enough.
アレライ そこにある My home
All right, right there is my home.
満ち足りるまで まだ走るなら 場所へと進んでゆく Be boy inside
Until I'm fully satisfied, I'll keep running forward to that place. Be boy inside!
The soul is divided
Colder inside, the dice
Roll is decisive, must have it nice
A gorgeous device to trick and entice, and it's got a price
切符は譲う 私のよう
My ticket is like mine,
ただハートは重石 後だりカフェをそそくそう then never gonna change
just a heavy heart... then never gonna change.
Lie to myself, reject any and all help
Betting all of my chips, let 'em fall to hell
Blood, sweat cannot stop the thoughts invading
じゃあアウトプット優しい ビーストじゃなきゃ噛み止めって願うなんて異常 おしまいもう魂すらも不要
Isn't it abnormal to wish for a gentle beast? It's over, I don't even need a soul.
Our world is turning once again
For that reason I still sing
And we've shed so many tears by now, though I'd never dare to change a thing
でも泣いて笑って 死にたくなった 日々も私なの
Yet, those days of crying, laughing, and wanting to die are also me.
この世界には もうこれ以上 何もない
In this world, there is nothing more than this.
Numbing pain is numbing happiness
Something anyone can find
Pushing on
For resolve that's truly mine
この絶望の風の中飛んでゆく
Flying through this wind of despair,
何を求めるの 運命に抗いやしないのに
what are you searching for, even though you won't resist fate?
そこにある幸せと戦い手に入れる
Fighting for the happiness right there to make it mine.
扉を開くその日まで
Until the day the door opens.
Your home is more than just a place you're never satisfied
その巣先は誰かに決められた道じゃなくて
That destination isn't a path decided by someone else,
私のもので'Cause I want be boy inside
it's my own, 'cause I want to be boy inside.
もう戻れない
Can't go back anymore.
In death, I'm somehow more alive
Hello again, my hideous foe
The tide is high, but I'm still low
You raise that gun like you're aiming for me, babe
Cut and run, we can never be free, yeah
There is never any goal
A hide and seek
Take a peek at the skill no one can teach
A dance with ideals that you know you'll never reach
Picking a random "want to be" to be "somebody"
Telephoned facts and poisoned wells
Ready or not now, boys and girls?
High up on your throne
Riding steady through the glow
Perfect sinners made of gold
People come and go
Only way that you can grow
Is not to give a damn at all
Whoa oh oh
Feel the drive
When hell's breaking loose, come and dance with me
Fever dies
I am what I am and they're out of my league
Can't catch up, but we're still in the fight
May never take the leap but I tell myself "don't mind"
'Cause I'm betting all on me
Still here burning with desire
Don't you tell me that you're tired
Are ya joking? maybe choking
While they're stoking up the fire
People say "you've lost your vision"
But you're seeing crystal clear
I'm making my own decisions before they let me disappear
What do you want from me? guessing we'll never agree
Believing everybody ends up drowning in their own damn entropy
インターネット 亡者 you're addicted like I told ya
Internet ghosts, you're addicted like I told ya
から回って 空になって そうさ みんな 燃えてこうや
Spinning your wheels, turning empty, yeah, everybody, let's burn up
People come and go
Only way that you can grow
Is not to give a damn at all
Whoa oh oh
Feel the drive
When hell's breaking loose, come and dance with me
Fever dies
I am what I am and they're out of my league
Can't catch up, but we're still in the fight
May never take the leap but I tell myself "don't mind"
'Cause I'm betting all on me
きみまくった妄想 あとに引けない焦燥
Delusions pushed to the limit, impatience you can't back down from
まきちらしてわめきだしてあたりちらし暴走
Scattering, screaming, going wildly out of control
何番煎じなのかわんねえ時のご都合大事に
Who knows how many times brewed, cherishing convenient timing
後生大事に堂々とかましてるけど
Acting all grand and pious, but...
文句も言わせんね 君のその agenda
Won't even let you complain about your agenda
Let it be known 消えろよ I will never surrender
Let it be known, disappear, I will never surrender
People come and go, there are highs and endless lows
Only way that you can grow is not to give a damn at all
Hello again, my hideous foe
The tide is high, but I'm not alone
Feel the drive
When hell's breaking loose, come and dance with me
Fever dies
I am what I am and they're out of my league
Can't catch up, but we're still in the fight
May never take the leap but I tell myself "don't mind"
'Cause I'm betting all on me
Feel the drive
When hell's breaking loose, come and dance with me
Fever dies
I am what I am and they're out of my league
Can't catch up, but we're still in the fight
May never take the leap but I tell myself "don't mind"
'Cause I'm betting all on me
Hah... so bored of easy prey
I need a bigger target to satisfy what I crave
Hah... I heard you wanna play?
My heel's on your neck, come on try and escape
Da-da-da-da-da-da-die
I gotcha in my sights, right now, still alive?
Seeing how I excite you, death's so deprived
Seeing how I excite you, death’s so deprived
I'm still the best at making y'all cry
Better get good, my my
Watching you from the shadows where I wander
暗闇で fear making me stronger
In the darkness, fear making me stronger
死神が止まらないんだ
The Grim Reaper can't be stopped
Very last breath, get a taste of death
One by one fall into my trap
Desiring the touch of a maniac
This is how it feels on the edge, 君の「the end」
This is how it feels on the edge, your "the end"
Take your very last breath for a taste of death
I’ve gotta hold back this lust
Vibe with it or bust
You can trust me, I got the stamina to be up with you all night
Giving you the run-around
I’m gonna chase ya down
‘Til I pin you to the ground
'Til I pin you to the ground
Sigh my name, boy, it’s my favorite sound
I gotcha in my sights, right now, still alive?
Seeing how I excite you, death’s so deprived
I'm still the best at making y'all die
Better get good, my my
Watching you from the shadows where I wander
暗闇で fear making me stronger
In the darkness, fear making me stronger
死神が止まらないんだ
The Grim Reaper can't be stopped
Very last breath, get a taste of death
One by one fall into my trap
Desiring the touch of a maniac
This is how it feels on the edge, 君の「the end」
This is how it feels on the edge, your "the end"
Take your very last breath for a taste of death
I just can't wait
To watch your heartbeat stop
Set my insides on fire
Seein’ your body drop
This darkness, warm and inviting
Come on inside, and don't fight me
Hearts accelerate, screaming, and biting
Leave me shaking, aching, pining
Let ‘chu subdue me and take this body and use me while death consumes you, girl I’ll make you choose me
Watching you from the shadows where I wander
暗闇で fear making me stronger
In the darkness, fear making me stronger
死神が止まらないんだ
The Grim Reaper can't be stopped
Very last breath, get a taste of death
One by one fall into my trap
Desiring the touch of a maniac
This is how it feels on the edge, 君の「the end」
This is how it feels on the edge, your "the end"
Take your very last breath for a taste of death
What I want is at my fingers
What now? Stop running
Ya know me as that chick who won’t back down, I'm coming
The gun who threatens your empire
A fire
An urge to be bad
You can’t expect to meet the angel that you had
Now! The tables have turned, hah
The bridges I burned with desire for human applause, plause
Rewind and relive and relay, all the 死 that I’ve wanted to say
Rewind and relive and relay, all the death that I’ve wanted to say
I beckon you all to be part of the making it known, my assent to the throne
Human kind’s got secret lusts
A voice to take them higher
I got no delusions, my own revolution
Your misconstrued myth come true
Come on! Make ’em afraid of ya
Make ’em afraid of ya
Guess I'm the queen of fools! They see what they wanna, no duh
Said to myself "no losing", make ’em afraid of ya
Ready to break some rules
An evil ya can’t help but love if you got the stuff to prove it, make ’em afraid of ya
Too far? I'm outta my mind
Chase the night, slay the light, feel the animal seeking a bite
Bare my teeth and cry out as I clench through the pain
Nay-sayers want nothing to change and their prayers are 邪邪邪魔!
Nay-sayers want nothing to change and their prayers are evil!
So what? Ya think I'm no good? Don’t act like gods should?
The joke ’s on you, the sky ’s their limit, disguise my ambitions
Make my own decisions
Defiant, on the brink, watch their kingdom start to fall
Human kind’s got secret lusts
A voice to take them higher
I'm ready and willin', so make me your villain
Your misconstrued myth come true, come on! Make ’em afraid of ya
what i want is at my fingers
(yeah, uh)
what now? stop running
ya know me as that chick who won't back down
i'm coming
the gun who threatens your empire
a fire
an urge to be bad
you can't expect to meet the angel that you had
now!
the tables have turned, hah
the bridges i burned with desire
for human applause, plause
rewind and relive and relay
all the 死 that i've wanted to say
i beckon you all to be part of
the making it known, my assent to the throne?
human kind's got secret lusts
a voice to take them higher
i got no delusions
my own revolution
your misconstrued myth come true
come on!
make 'em afraid of ya
hey! na na na na
yeah, yeah
make 'em afraid of ya
guess i'm the queen of fools!
they see what they wanna, no duh
said to myself \"no losing
make 'em afraid of ya\"
ready to break some rules
an evil ya can't help but love
if you got the stuff to prove it
make 'em afraid of ya
too far?
i'm outta my mind
chase the night
slay the light
feel the animal seeking a bite
bare my teeth and cry out as i clench through the pain
nay-sayers want nothing to change
and their prayers are 邪邪邪魔!
And their prayers are 邪邪邪魔！
so what?
ya think i'm no good?
don't act like gods should
the joke's on you, the sky's their limit
disguise my ambitions
make my own decisions
defiant, on the brink
watch their kingdom start to fall
human kind's got secret lusts
a voice to take them higher
i'm ready and willin'
so make me your villain
your misconstrued myth come true
come on!
make 'em afraid of ya
hey! na na na na
guess i'm the queen of fools!
they see what they wanna, no duh
said to myself \"no losing
make 'em afraid of ya\"
where to begin?
in this wicked world
there's a million others just like you
you talk too much, you're all out of touch
猿回しの猿になれない存在
猿回しの猿になれない存在。
you talk too much, you're all out of touch
猿回しの猿になれない存在
猿回しの猿になれない存在。
yeah, it's anything goes
when you're forced to create while advancing on tiptoes
actually worthless, got no purpose
they'll replace you, deface all your work
it's the point of \"you'll never return from this
learn from us
no rebuilding the bridges that burned for us
getting superfluous, smiles and waves
the praise in abundance to make sure you stay
so the story goes \"you're the one
they'll remember, lie, call it \"labors of love
why put in the effort?
cuz you're not special, none of us are
even those plagued by stardom fade into dust
nothing matters
who the hell else should i be?
a puppet, a pawn, if i fail i'm gone
so everyone else can be happy
with no question, i fall in line
believing promises every time
soldier onward, spare me your honesty
cuz i know my place now, a washed out prophecy
out of sight, out of mind
we'll never see the same view
got so lost, so exhausted, but you can't give in
catch on fire, you're admired
forget the ones who saved you
there's no bias, the noblest never win
so we close our eyes and pretend
that this might mend
right, just a means to an end
why put up a fight, then?
cuz you're not special, none of us are
even those plagued by stardom fade into dust
nothing matters
how much more love can i spend?
a puppet, a pawn, if i fail i'm gone
so everyone fallen can ascend?
with no question, i fall in line
and play my part so the chosen shine
persona non grata, better left out of the sun
cuz i know my place now
those watching raise a glass to the bad news come to pass
a million eyes demand an encore 'till the very last
reach out to find my whereabouts, my own way
each moment passing is a debt i gotta pay now
just look me in the eyes, it's time they realize
the mountaintop means nothing if you don't gotta climb
survive, want me on your front lines
so you can take and when it's over, leave nothing behind
so the story goes \"you're the one
they'll remember, lie, call it \"labors of love
why put in the effort?
cuz you're not special, none of us are
even those plagued by stardom fade into dust
nothing matters
who the hell else should i be?
a puppet, a pawn, if i fail i'm gone
so everyone else can be happy
I am the picture of a perfect human every day
An icon of god, not programmed to make any mistakes
I am notorious for staying in my lane
'Cause I got what's on the mannequin with no right to complain
Animosity is permanent, some days I can't get up
If I showed a bit of weakness I don't think it would let up
Numbers crushing me, pinning me down, I will not let you see me frowning
In reality I'm drowning, someone save me now
I am the picture of a perfect human every day
and I kind of got enough a grab to make any mistake
I am notorious for staying in my lane
'Cause I got what's on the mannequin with no right to complain
Animosity is permanent, some days I can't get up
If I showed a bit of weakness I don't think it would let up
Numbers crushing me, pinning me down, I will not let you see me frowning
In reality I'm drowning, someone save me now
この 世界 に 全く 意味 ない
There is no meaning in this world at all
狂っ ちゃ って いい
It's fine to go crazy
Feeling like the pen's run out at last
Living like a moth beneath the glass
Ever just a slave unto my past
I just laugh
If you retreat now, this life will never change
Just like lyrics you've heard a thousand times, tired uninspired refrains
Days on repeat cloud my mind, am I deranged?
When I can hear that fractious anthem in my heart again
I swear I'm gonna break the chain
We're living in the upside down now
We're living in the upside down
Some call it "niche", others call it just "unlikeable"
But this here is an opera where actors are recyclable
I'm breaking parole, stand out, I won't be controlled
My hand is stronger than ever and yet I fold
No time left for a fallen empress
The void ahead is ever tall and endless
Defenseless, expendable
Pretend that I'm still dependable
Told I don't belong near my own friends
There's no end
And nothing's getting better
So I'm thinking of pushing and pulling myself and seeing how far I bend
この 世界 で 生き たく ない
I don't want to live in this world
死ん じゃ って いい
It's fine to just die
Feeling like there's nothing left to write
Living like I'm running out of time
Ever losing sleep wondering why I can't die
逃げ出 , 人生 は 変わら ない
If you run away, life will never change
何 回 聞い た こと が ある
How many times have I heard that?
歌 が 回っ てる 、 永遠 に
Lyrics are spinning around forever
I really need you now though life may never change
I want to scream how I feel until I'm gone, rising above the outrage
Days of defeat, loses always stain the page
So I'll create an undying anthem in my heart again
Tonight I'm gonna break the chain
We're living in the upside down now
We're living in the upside down
I am the picture of a perfect human every day
layout in a little bit,
but right now I wanted to introduce you guys to the crowd.
but right now I wanted to introduce you
guys to the crowd.
Guys,
jikoshokai!
time for self-introductions!
Hi, IRyS,
it's IRyS from Hololive English.
Your seiso nephilim here to bring hope,
and I am the positive energy in the Wheel of Fortune card thingy that we're...
and I am the positive energy in the
Wheel of Fortune card thingy that we're...
Is that what you think?
Is that your guess on it?
'Cause it's hope and chaos.
Obviously, obviously!
Hope is like, you know, the good stuff, uh-huh, right?
Hope is like, you know, the good stuff,
uh-huh, right?
And so this is the bad stuff over here, is that what you're trying to say?
And so this is the bad stuff over here,
is that what you're trying to say?
Hey, not me, that's her!
She said it, she said it, not me!
I do?
Yeah, that's right.
I'm bad! She's bad!
What's up?
I am Chaos, the end of end!
A cute rat trapped in a cage of her skill-issue best friend.
A cute rat trapped in a cage of her
skill-issue best friend.
I just... Oh my god, I'm like drooling.
You're less than... I'm just from Hololive English! Witness me!
You're less than... I'm just from
Hololive English! Witness me!
Am I the bad side?
There's no such thing as a bad side in Wheel of Fortune.
There's no such thing as a bad side
in Wheel of Fortune.
What? Wheel of Fortune is like gacha, right?
And if you get like the good results, oh...
And then if you get like the bad... There is no such thing as a bad result, it's chaos!
And then if you get like the bad...
There is no such thing as a bad result, it's chaos!
You guys want to know the real the real wheel the real Wheel of Reason the Wheel of Reason? Stop, stop it, stop it, oh my at her!
You guys want to know the real...
the real Wheel of Reason? Stop it, stop it, oh my god!
Okay, the reason that I chose you guys for Wheel of Fortune is because I am so fortunate to have met you both.
Okay, the reason that I chose you guys
for Wheel of Fortune is because I am so fortunate to have met you both.
Oh, my life!
tetete tetete tetete te we
Now, but seriously, you guys' guesses were pretty good, too.
Now, but seriously, you guys' guesses
were pretty good, too.
You guys just seemed very Wheel of Fortune-esque, so that's why I chose you guys.
You guys just seemed very
Wheel of Fortune-esque, so that's why I chose you guys.
What did you guys think about performing together? Was it fun? I loved it! That shit was so much fun.
What did you guys think about performing together?
Was it fun? I loved it! That shit was so much fun.
I'm a picture of a perfect human every day!
We had so much fun!
I love how like whenever the camera went to like each of you guys, like you could see your personality. Like Bae's all like, you know, like she's just like that. And then and then IRyS is like smiling and cute like like like idol like like my diva, my diva, my princess.
I love how like whenever the camera went
to like each of you guys, like you could see your personality.
Like Bae's all like, you know, like she's just like that.
And then and then IRyS is like smiling and cute
like like like idol like like my diva, my diva, my princess.
I'm so... Yeah, it's very cute. I don't know, it made my heart go like ba-bum. I felt so cool singing it though, like yeah, yeah, I'm a picture of a perfect human every day!
I'm so... Yeah, it's very cute. I don't know,
it made my heart go like ba-bum.
I felt so cool singing it though, like yeah, yeah,
I'm a picture of a perfect human every day!
So cool! Get into your feelings, you know. Seikai kitakku na!
So cool! Get into your feelings, you know.
Seikai kitakku na!
Not unless you die starving trying to find your way out of here, but I'm not going to help you guys. You have to do that yourself. Time to go bye-bye.
Not unless you die starving trying to find
your way out of here, but I'm not going to help you guys.
You have to do that yourself. Time to go bye-bye.
Okay, we're being kicked out? Wait, I'll look this way. Okay. I'll go this way. Okay. Are you pretty sure that there's like an empress here? Okay. We're racing? We're wrestling out? Give us a countdown. Ready? Like a race queen. Okay. Three, two, one, pew!
Okay, we're being kicked out? Wait,
I'll look this way. Okay. I'll go this way.
Okay. Are you pretty sure that there's like an empress here?
Okay. We're racing? We're wrestling out?
Give us a countdown. Ready? Like a race queen.
Okay. Three, two, one, pew!
Off to the races they go! Those are maximum silliness. Anyway, I had to kick them out because guess what, guys, it's my birthday, which means that... there is merchandise. There is merchandise and goods for you guys, so check it out, okay? I will introduce each merch item at one time. Hope you guys are ready. There is some limited stuff this time, so hope you guys are ready to grab it real quick. Now, first up is...
Off to the races they go!
Those are maximum silliness.
Anyway, I had to kick them out because guess what, guys,
it's my birthday, which means that... there is merchandise.
There is merchandise and goods for you guys, so check it out, okay?
I will introduce each merch item at one time.
Hope you guys are ready. There is some limited stuff this time,
so hope you guys are ready to grab it real quick.
Now, first up is...
Mystical Songstress... Oh wait, hold on a second. First of all, take a look at all of this, right? There's a Mystical Songstress poster. I'm sorry, I don't know where I'm looking ever, any second of the day. This is a poster. I know you guys like posters, so it was recommended to me. This time, let's do a poster that features the main key visual of the merchandise. It is drawn by Kunoru Norari-sensei. Arigatou gozaimasu! Thank you so much!
Mystical Songstress... Oh wait, hold on a second.
First of all, take a look at all of this, right?
There's a Mystical Songstress poster. I'm sorry,
I don't know where I'm looking ever, any second of the day.
This is a poster. I know you guys like posters,
so it was recommended to me. This time, let's do a poster
that features the main key visual of the merchandise.
It is drawn by Kunoru Norari-sensei. Arigatou gozaimasu!
Thank you so much!
Second is Lucky Dead Beat's Random Rubber Strap. You can get one random design out of four possible designs. The illustration is by Keijou-sensei. There are lots of different outfits, and so I don't know, if you want, you can try to collect all four, you know. I'm pretty sure that you can grab them separate. So try to get all of them, okay? Yes, yes.
Second is Lucky Dead Beat's Random Rubber Strap.
You can get one random design out of four possible designs.
The illustration is by Keijou-sensei.
There are lots of different outfits, and so I don't know,
if you want, you can try to collect all four, you know.
I'm pretty sure that you can grab them separate.
So try to get all of them, okay? Yes, yes.
Now, the third item is—I know you guys have been waiting for this—Underworld University Sweater! The same design as my recently released new outfit. Kawaii, right? Like kawaii! You can wear the same sweater that I do, yatta! Hope you guys grab it, it's very comfy.
Now, the third item is—I know you guys have been waiting
for this—Underworld University Sweater!
The same design as my recently released new outfit.
Kawaii, right? Like kawaii!
You can wear the same sweater that I do, yatta!
Hope you guys grab it, it's very comfy.
Next up, fourth is Stay HYDRATED! Water Bottle. Okay, you can use this when heading off to work or traveling, you know, Deadbeats, we love to drink water. Despite the fact that a lot of you guys are skeletons, you still need water, right, to live. I mean, that's just those are just the rules. I don't make them. So make sure that you stay hydrated with your special Mori Calliope water bottle. It's very subtle. Nobody'll know that you're like a big Holo fan, but the ones that are also...
Next up, fourth is Stay HYDRATED! Water Bottle.
Okay, you can use this when heading off to work or traveling,
you know, Deadbeats, we love to drink water.
Despite the fact that a lot of you guys are skeletons,
you still need water, right, to live.
I mean, that's just those are just the rules.
I don't make them. So make sure that you stay hydrated
with your special Mori Calliope water bottle.
It's very subtle. Nobody'll know that you're like
a big Holo fan, but the ones that are also...
Hololive fans will know.
Yeah, that's what I'm trying to do these days, so I hope you guys enjoy.
Fifth item is a situational voice pack, "The Fortune I Got from the Dark Forest Songstress."
It sounds so silly. It's like maximum freaking silliness,
like some kind of isekai anime title.
I hope you guys enjoy it. I think it's very cute and fits the theme of the main illustration.
Also, if you buy the full set for a limited number of orders, you can get the hand-autographed postcard. Rest in peace, Mori's hand.
But there actually really aren't many this time that I'm doing because, you know, rest in peace, Mori's hand. I got to watch out for my hand health and I'm very busy, so make sure that you grab yours. They're a very limited supply, okay?
For the normal set, there is a foil-stamped postcard included instead, and this was drawn by Kuno Norati-sensei. Thank you so much again.
You will receive also—this is big—a card that can be used in the
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME as a thank-you bonus for the complete set of premium talent merchandise.
This is the only time you can grab it! Do not miss out on it! This card will only be given to customers who purchase the complete set
of premium talent merchandise... wait, purchased from the Hololive Production official shop, sorry. Words, English, HoloEN, everybody.
given to customers who purchased from the Hololive Production official shop, okay?
And this bonus card is an Oshi Holomem card, and you can only use one of these in the game,
and it is used to show love for your Oshi, so show some love for Mori, okay?
Now, for more details on the card and the rules of the game, please visit the official page of the Hololive Official Card Game, and do note that the card only comes in Japanese.
So, with that being said, everybody, we still have a little bit more of the show to go.
Are you guys ready to continue?
Let's keep having lots of fun, because we still got a couple performances left, okay? Are you guys watching? It's about to get even crazier!
Let's go!
In ages forgotten, a reaper was born
Spinning tales of deadly belief
A yearning to traverse that forest of thorns
In remembrance of what lie beneath
The dangers abounding, the horrors untold
Cloud my vision, 'till I cannot see
Peculiar enchantments begin to unfold
And the underworld calls back to me
As the light grows dimmer and fades...
Cross that river now
Make our way beyond the gates
Release from our confinement, together, we'll find it
The trail is fraught with perils and yet, we don't mind it
But looking towards horizons reminding me of then, can't repent
Though I've hardly been spent
A journey downward toward somewhere new, yet familiar
I'm learning how to stand for the smile I swear to defend
Till the end, as we further descend, then, shall we go?
To be swallowed by fates below
A moment in history, a flicker in time
A mystery I still can't break through
I'm deathly defiant of crossing that line
I don't want to break down before you...
Reach downward to glory, yet upward - what for?
An ouroboros of earthly desire
Devouring my tale just to tell it once more
Am I still the gold statue you admire?
Collecting all the stories we've enjoyed
And reflecting on the thorns that near destroyed me
I sang about a journey's end, and now we come upon
Another one, the sun setting earlier than believed
From this point downward, I cannot return
For the final dream I sought is so close yet far within my reach
Though I'd like it to be known, this I made on my own
Release from our confinement, together we'll find it
The trail is fraught with perils, and maybe all is as it should be
I promise I'll still be me
My mistakes, somehow made a good story great
A journey downward toward somewhere new, yet familiar
I'm learning how to stand for the smiles I swear to defend
Till the end, as we further descend, then
Shall we go?
Swallowed up by what waits below
Minasan, what did you guys think about our performance today? Oh my gosh, it was so fun.
Minasan, what did you guys think about our performance today?
Oh my gosh, it was so fun.
Hey, wait a minute though, it's not over yet so don't leave, don't leave. Don't run away to go get the limited merch or anything like that.
Hey, wait a minute though, it's not over yet so don't leave, don't leave.
Don't run away to go get the limited merch or anything like that.
It's not time yet because we still have a little bit more to go.
You guys are going to miss the grand finale so just stay right there. But um, yeah, no this show was amazing. We didn't have a lot of MCs,
You guys are going to miss the grand finale so just stay right there.
But um, yeah, no this show was amazing. We didn't have a lot of MCs,
but that's because, you know, we were working hard to perform for you guys.
And look at all these tarot cards that we have here of me and all of my friends together. You know, I wanted to celebrate holoive original songs,
And look at all these tarot cards that we have here of me and all of my friends together.
You know, I wanted to celebrate holoive original songs,
especially by Mori this time. I'm a big believer in like let's go hololive original music!
especially by Mori this time.
I'm a big believer in like let's go hololive original music!
And I wanted to celebrate all of that with you guys today by singing some of my favorite songs by me, together with my friends.
And so I hope that you guys were able to enjoy today's showing. Take a look at this stage.
And so I hope that you guys were able to enjoy today's showing.
Take a look at this stage.
Isn't the stage amazing? I know that we looked at it a little bit earlier before, but
Isn't the stage amazing?
I know that we looked at it a little bit earlier before, but
I mean, it's basically like a a dream venue for me. So sparkly and beautiful, oh my gosh.
I mean, it's basically like a a dream venue for me.
So sparkly and beautiful, oh my gosh.
It's been so amazing and getting to explore all the different tarot cards as well with you guys, because you know, as as, as you know,
the arcana is the means by which all is revealed, right? And so I hope that you guys had some fun
the arcana is the means by which all is revealed, right?
And so I hope that you guys had some fun
getting to kind of like see my choices of songs, and who I chose to sing in each song and stuff like that. But but we got to move right along,
getting to kind of like see my choices of songs, and who I chose to sing in each song and stuff like that.
But but we got to move right along,
we got to move right along because, as you may have noticed, a special premiere has showed up on my channel,
and our last guest might have something to do with that. This is a performance I'm very excited about. I got to go change really quickly,
and our last guest might have something to do with that.
This is a performance I'm very excited about. I got to go change really quickly,
but in the meantime,
let's go ahead and summon one more person to the stage. Are you guys ready? Without further ado...
let's go ahead and summon one more person to the stage.
Are you guys ready? Without further ado...
Here we go! Woyao!
Minasan, saigo noゲスト wa nanto! TOOBE-san desu!
Okay, everyone, here's our final guest. It's TOOBE-san!
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
Great to be here.
Great to have you! Great to be here.
Hajimemashite.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, yeah.
I guess this would be my first time greeting most of your viewers? Yeah, sounds about right. It's a pleasure to be here.
I guess this would be my first time greeting most of your viewers?
Yeah, sounds about right. It's a pleasure to be here.
Hai, yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
And it's a pleasure to have you.
Jitsu wa, ano... nanka TOOBE-san wa... ano... kyonen no... ano kariope no Spotify de ichiban yoku kiiteta no wa jitsu datta nante kedo...
Believe it or not, TOOBE-san, you were my most listened to artist on Spotify last year.
Arigatou gozaimasu sonna...
Thank you so much.
No, thank you.
Iie iie, kochira koso nanka hololive ni hairu mae zutto fan desu kara. Hontou ni ureshii desu ne.
I've been a fan of yours since before I joined hololive, even.
Really? I'm so happy to have you here.
Ya, kochira koso kyoshuku desu ne. Hai, sou desu ne...
Please, you flatter me.
I think your songs are really cool. For real.
Ano TOOBE-san no kyoku wa... hontou ni kakkouii to omou. Maji de, nanka, merodi no sensei ga yabai desu, hontou ni.
Your taste in melodies is actually crazy.
Thank you.
Sou desu ne. Soshite nanka makeinu no hanashi ga sugoi suki dakara, liriku mo mecchakucha omoshiroi to omou de... hai, issho ni kyoku tsukuritai na to omoimashita.
And I love a good underdog story, so your lyrics really hit home, too.
It really made me want to work on a song with you.
Arigatou gozaimasu, hai. Zehi tanoshikatta desu, hontou ni.
Thank you. Working with you was a lot of fun.
I'm glad it was. Thank you.
Soshite, ano watashi to TOOBE-san wa chotto ano kyoutsuuten ga aru ndakedo, ano, shourai no yume wa mangaka datta.
What's more, TOOBE-san and I have something in common.
We both dreamed of being manga artists.
Aa, sou desu ne. Sou desu, sou desu, sou desu.
Oh yeah, that's right.
Hai. Dakara, konkai animeshon myujikubideo tsukurou kana to omoimashita.
That's why we thought we should make an animated music video for this one.
Hai. Sou, konkai kyarakutaa dezaan wa kariope to TOOBE-san.
Yeah. TOOBE-san and I designed the characters.
So, animeshon wa kariope desu. Sou nan desu.
Right. And I made the animation.
そうですよね。なんかの
That's right.
あれですよね。僕あんまり、あの、まぁ絵柄が多分相当違うものなので、どうしようかなと思ったんですけど、
It's like, our art styles are really different,
どうしようかなと思ったんですけど、その
so I was wondering how we would do this.
せっかくならお互いの良さが出せるようなアニメ作れるといいなってことで、
But we decided to aim for an anime MV that'd showcase both of our styles.
僕もちょっとその全体の話し、何て言うんですか、プロットとかも考えましたし、キャラクターもちょっと1体か2体描かせていただいて、
I worked with you on the overall plot and story, and designed a couple of characters.
はい。
Yeah.
まとまりましたね。はい。
And it all came together.
そうだな。なかなか面白いMVになりましたから、皆さんぜひこの後チェックしてほしい。はい。
Yeah, it's quite a fun and entertaining music video, so please check it out, guys.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
じゃあ、どんな曲を作ったかな?
I bet everyone's wondering what the song is like.
じゃあ、はい。
So let's have them listen to it!
皆さんに聴かせましょう。はい。
Yeah.
いくぞ!
Okay, here we go!
TOBOE x カリオペ 新曲「セピア」、チェックアウト!
Tobo x Calliope new song, "Sepia", check it out!
誤解すんなよ 孤独げな
Don't misunderstand, it's laughable
サッと過ぎ去るエブリデイは
How time flashes by every day
another prisoner of fate no one could fake out
stay awake now, you know you wanna fire away
now there's no question where the fault lies these days I struggle just to empathize
もう戻らないって分かっているんだろ?
There's no going back, and you know that
cast a blessing on my cursed role
and feed this bleeding egotistical soul
before you know it, it's the moment you've lost all control
遠き日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I wonder why I came to be
あぁ美しい青い日々だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
I should burn their images into mind
もう少し強くなる前とね
But I'd have to be a little stronger first
身分不相応の嫉妬に塗れた ちょっと足りないエクスタシー
Dripping in jealousy that's a bit too daring, an ecstasy that's just a little bit lacking
誤解も解けないまま私を傷つけて
I hurt somebody without ever opening my eyes
一粒の才能すらいないわ 転がり落ちたジゴロサイ
There's no talent here, it's clear to see, the rigged dice falls and rolls
貴方の愛に気付けないまま
Before I ever notice your love and affection
cast a blessing on my cursed heart
why keep me breathing while it's falling apart?
どうか神様教えてくれますか
Pray tell me, God
言葉少なにあなたに捧ぐ
I give to you silently
今にも消えてしまいそうなこの命を
My life that's about to burn out
あぁ愛おしいセピア色した何より大事なこの景色をもっと見ていたいよな
Ah, and these sepia-toned sights, most precious of all that I wish I could watch some more
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
everything I ever wanted was in front of me
the angels on my shoulder still cannot agree
if I was somebody else, could I get everything?
I'm always gonna be my own worst enemy
everything I ever wanted was in front of me
the devils on my shoulder never let me be
obsessing over tomorrows that I'll never see
somebody save me, my world is caving in cuz I thought I deserved it all for free
遠き日の夢を見るたび
Every time I dream of days gone by
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I wonder why I came to be
あぁ美しい青い日々だな
Ah, such beautiful, youthful days
この目に焼き付けておこうかな
I should burn their images into mind
もう少し強くなる前とね
But I'd have to be a little stronger first
皆さん、聴いてくれてありがとうございます!またね!
Thank you so much, everyone! See you later!
Catch you on the flip side. Peace!